http://www.maddak.com/pages.php?page=privacy

Online Retailers | Store Locator | Customer Service | My Account
We are an Essential Business & Open!   SP COVID19 Preparedness
SHOP NOW
Rika ProductsAssessment Tools for Occupational TherapistsBariatric ProductsBath SafetyBedroom AidsDressing AidsDrinking AidsEating AidsHand AidsKitchen/Household AidsLeisure/Recreation AidsMobility AidsPersonal CarePediatric Adaptive ProductsReachersReading/Writing AidsSafety AidsSilipos Innovative Gel Products for the Feet, Hands and SkinTenura Anti-Slip and Grip ProductsTherapists, Nurses and Caregivers
SHOP by Condition
Alzheimer's/DementiaArthritisAsthmaAutismBack InjuryBariatrics/ObesityBrain Injury/CognitiveCerebral PalsyDevelopmental DelaysHand WeaknessHip Replacement/InjuryKnee/Leg InjuryLearning DisabilitiesMobilityMultiple SclerosisMuscular DystrophyOsteoporosisParkinson'sSpinal Cord InjuryStroke
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We at SP Industries know you care about how information you provide us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy describes how we gather information from you when you visit the Maddak Inc. web site located at www.maddak.com (the “Site”) and how we may use and share that information. By visiting our site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
In this Privacy Policy, the words “we,” ‘us” and “our” refer to Maddak Inc.
Please note that this Privacy Policy only addresses our Site’s privacy practices, and does not address the privacy practices of our distributors. For information about the privacy practices of a particular distributor, please consult that distributor’s Web site.
The Information We Collect
We do not collect your name, address or other personally identifiable information from you when you visit our Site unless you provide us with the information voluntarily (for example, when placing an order on our Site). We do use standard “cookie” technology to collect non-personal information to enhance your experience on our Site. Cookies are small packets of data that a web site stores on a user’s computer’s hard drive so that their computer will “remember” information about their visit. We also record “session information” such as information about what you have added to your shopping cart during your visit to our Site.
Sharing Your Information
We do not share your personally identifiable information with any third parties except in the ordinary course of administering our business and as required by law. For example, we may use outside service providers to deliver products you order. Any such service providers will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions and to the extent permitted by law. When ordering products, we will ask you to specify a distributor that will be credited with your order. This distributor will have access to information regarding which products you have ordered. In addition, we may release your personally identifiable information when we are required to do so by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency; or whenever we believe that disclosing this information is necessary or advisable, for example, to protect the rights, property, or our safety or that of others. In the event of a sale or merger of our business, your personally identifiable information then held by us would be transferred to our successor.
Removal From Mailing List
If at any time you decide that you would like to stop receiving communications from us, please email your request to: ecatalogs@maddak.com. Once we receive your request, we will take reasonable efforts to promptly remove you from our mailing list.
Security
We have reasonable security measures in place intended to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personally identifiable information that we have collected from you at the Site. However, we are unable to guarantee that the security measures we take will not be penetrated or compromised or that your personally identifiable information will remain secure under all circumstances.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on our web site as soon as they go into effect. Please be aware that, to the extent permitted by applicable law, our use of information is governed by the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we use the information. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy and use of our website, please email us at data.protection@spindustries.com. Data access requests should also be emailed be to data.protection@spindustries.com - Please state "Data Access Request" in the subject, include the type of access request you desire and send from the email address you wish to have updated.
About Maddak  |
Careers  |
Resource Center  |
Product Instructions
News & Events   |
Product Warranty  |
Privacy Policy  |
Directions  |
